Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[This program is intended for
audiences aged 13 and over]
[It may contain
explicit visuals, audio, and content;
viewers under the age of 13
should be advised]
These are the photos of my family.
I have twin brothers,
Jimmy and Junior,
and another brother named Justin.
But after the decision to transition,
Justin changed her name to Jasmine.
Jimmy, Junior, Justin...
everyone has two-syllable nicknames.
Even our dog was named Jelly.
But when the youngest one arrived,
they decided to give her
a one-syllable nickname, Jane.
We are a small, cozy family
who prefers to keep to ourselves.
But the neighbors are always
poking around in our business.
It was this auntie
who tattled on Jasmine with that photo.
I guess she has too much free time,
so she decided to spend it
on our family stuff.
Little girl,
you got into university this year?
Yes.
What did you choose to major in?
Do you want to be a teacher
like your mom?
No, I chose Fine and Applied Arts.
Huh? Like drawing and all that?
How are you gonna put food
on the table with that degree?
Well, by cooking.
Brat!
You're getting on my nerves!
How did they raise these kids?
Jane,
I brought some desserts for you,
but I haven't seen you since yesterday.
Are you okay?
Would you like me
to keep you company?
[It's okay. I'm fine]
I'm not okay at all.
Jane?
Jane, eat something, alright?
I caused you so much trouble...
Not at all.
I want to take care of you, Jane.
Well, don't you wanna know
what happened to me?
Of course, I do,
but I just didn't want to ask.
I believe everyone
has their own private life,
but if you wanna share, I'm here.
My childhood dog...
passed away.
Everyone has to go through
the loss of something they love.
Jelly wasn't just something I love.
She was family,
a friend,
an encouragement,
someone who was there for me
through every moment of my life.
Right now, she has happily
crossed the rainbow bridge.
If she looks down from above
and sees her loved one crying,
not eating, or sleeping,
she'd probably be heartbroken
for making you feel this way.
This is so ridiculous of me, right?
Not at all.
If it were me, I'd be very sad, too.
But I do want you to know
that no matter how sad you are,
you'll have to accept the reality
and live in the present.
Be strong, alright?
From now on, come rain or shine,
you'll always see me
right next to you.
I'll always be your strength
and your supporter, Jane.
Dai...
Yes?
I want you to hug me.
Excuse me, then.
You and Dai are too chill.
Even after you both feel the same,
you're still in a talking stage?
Playing hard to get much?
Well...
Who'd be as hasty as you, Waii?
Me?
What about me?
I don't think
you and Orn are just friends.
I found photos of you
on her Facebook account,
going to pubs one after another.
And don't deny it.
There was also NewYear,
who you got hooked on instantly
when you first met.
So what?
Are you a lesbian, Waii?
Alright!
So what if I am?
Are you not
gonna be friends with me anymore?
What? Why are you sulking?
Cake and I just wish
you wouldn't hide it from us.
Mm.
Well, I'm just afraid
you wouldn't take it,
but that feeling's all gone now...
Because I have JaneWill on my side.
Well, what about you, Cake?
Any thoughts?
No, girl.
I love gentlemen.
So, what's going on
between you and Dai?
Well, not much.
I think that people
need to take things slow,
like I'm doing now.
Take things slow...
There you go again.
If you guys were a novel,
you'd be over 100 chapters long.
She's right. Why beat around the bush?
- Mm.
- I only see Dai trying to win you over.
You should do something to reciprocate,
like asking her out
for a movie, a date, or...
meeting your parents.
Facts.
- Meeting my parents?
- Mm.
NewYear...
Why are you waiting?
Can we go back to where we were?
We never seem to change.
God made a man and a woman
for each other,
not for women to love each other.
God made humans,
but He doesn't force anyone
to live a certain way.
Everyone should be free to love
whoever they want.
No way.
I don't want this.
Please don't date that Waii.
But I will.
If you insist on going out with her,
I'll also date boys.
It's your life.
You don't believe me, do you?
I'll show you!
What's the matter, Pangpond?
I don't want to live.
My life is over.
Your friend is an a**hole
for turning NewYear into a lesbian!
Waii is not the only one to blame.
If that girl didn't play along,
it'd be the end of the story, right?
So it's my fault?
You wouldn't even take my side now,
would you?
Good.
Then, you'll see the last of me!
What kind of man are you
to be so stupid?
Your parents raised you well.
They spoiled you
and made sure
you had everything you wanted,
just for you
to think about ending it all
because of a girl?!
Moron!
That's why she doesn't love you.
You can't force people
not to love each other.
But you can make yourself worthy
so that they love you back.
If you want to win the battle,
you'll have to fight.
Change yourself,
so she regrets her decision.
Understood?
- Yes...
- Come here.
There, there, you little puppy.
You're such a crybaby.
Would you like to join my family
for somtam this week?
[Can I?]
Order me some spicy somtam
this Sunday.
I'll bring a senior home.
My, my, was it the same one
you always talked to me about?
Why haven't you told me
about this, sweetie?
Whoa, is someone after my little sister?
Alright, Jane. Leave it to me.
Is it really just a 'senior'?
Junior, Jasmine.
No one has answered Dad's question.
Hm?
He'll find out this Sunday.
Hello, Dad?
The senior I'm bringing home
is a girl.
Oh...
That's a relief.
I thought it was a boy.
Dai was last year's campus queen
and is now a sophomore in Architecture.
Mm-hm...
That's good, sweetie.
When you have older friends
from school,
they can step in to take care of you
if something happens.
Dai has been taking the best care of me.
She's been giving me rides,
buying me desserts,
and she even told me she liked me.
Hm?
Liked you?
In what way, sweetie?
She's asking me out.
Hello?
I think our call's been disconnected.
No, no, sweetie.
Jane,
let me get this straight.
You're telling me
you're a lesbian, right?
It's just that...
I just want to make sure
you like this girl,
but that you're also
into men in general.
What do you mean?
I only want to make sure
that I still have the chance
at grandchildren.
I don't want to deny who I am.
Also, I don't want you to have hopes
that I'll go out with a man someday.
And I think I'm a lesbian.
What makes you think that?
I don't think
you should decide this so soon.
I watched straight porn,
and it didn't make me
feel anything special.
But it thrills me seeing women naked.
Mm...
Hey!
Our colors match.
How cute.
Dai...
- Give me a sec to book a ride.
- Mm!
Are you hungry?
I've got a ride for us.
Let's go.
Jimmy, clean it properly.
Yes, just like that.
- Yes, Mom.
- Oh, Mild.
That's good. Make it nice and neat.
Oh, my goodness!
Why are my frames in such a mess?
Please arrange them for me.
And straighten my photo,
so everyone can see my face.
You're doing great, sweetie.
For heaven's sake!
Look at this dust, Jasmine!
- Yes, Mom?
- Jasmine, sweetie.
Here, take a cloth
and clean the area in front of the TV.
Goodness, it's incredibly dusty!
- Hurry up.
- Sure, Mom.
Alright, clean it properly
so that it's nice and clean.
- Oh, my goodness! Honey!
- Huh?
Lift your feet up!
- What's the matter?
- Look at how dusty this is!
- Junior?
- Yes?
Sweep this over here!
- Sorry, Dad.
- Please do it.
That's right. That's it, son.
- Where's the dust?
- Let's see.
Junior, why haven't you
- put your broom under it?
- I'm sorry, Mom.
- Honey, lift your feet!
- I'm sorry, Dad.
- Whoa, whoa!
- Jeez, make it quick!
- You're blocking my way!
- Jeez...
- Whatever makes you happy, honey.
Whatever makes you happy.
- Honey, be honest with me.
- What?
Why do we have to rush the cleaning
at this minute?
Well, we have a very special guest
joining us today.
"A very special guest..."
Honey...
If you don't want to lend a hand,
stop interrupting.
Go sit outside
if it's such an inconvenience.
Please.
- Jeez...
- Go sit outside, Honey.
Fine!
I'm an outsider in this family now.
Honey, you don't even care
to arrange the pillows after yourself.
Jeez, we need to make it nice and tidy.
Kids, hurry up, alright?
- Yes.
Yes, Mom.
Are you really not
gonna change your profile pic?
You're gonna keep using my drawing?
Don't you want to change it
to your pretty face?
I'd rather show everyone
that the cutest cartoonist
gave me her drawing.
Honestly, the picture you drew of me
looks even better
than I do in real life.
Hello, Mom.
- Hi, there.
- Hello.
This is my mom and Junior,
and this is Dai, my senior.
You're such a beautiful girl.
No wonder
you were the campus queen.
- Thank you.
- Who even told you that, Mom?
We'd better go inside now.
Come on in.
Let's go.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, sweetie.
Why are you out here in all this heat?
Well, your mom chased me out here,
telling me I was blocking her way.
Do you also read
'Phon Nikorn Kimngwan,' Dad?
Have you heard of this series?
My dad used to find these
for me to read, too.
They're pretty fun
and a good insight into how people lived
80 years ago in Bangkok.
Certainly.
I love reading it.
We have more than
100 books from this series.
We have to mention this one, too,
an edition with all the highlights
from different books.
It's such a great read, sweetie!
How nice.
I'm definitely
going to look for one to read.
Don't bother looking for one.
I'm about to finish this one,
and you can borrow it once I do.
You can give it back to me
after you finish reading it.
- Really?
- Of course.
Thank you.
I think we should continue
this conversation inside.
Otherwise, the food I warmed up
would get cold.
Let's go, kids.
Whoa, is this a graduation party?
What?!
After all, my daughter
is bringing a guest home.
Dai, you're the first friend
she's ever invited to our house.
- True.
- That's right.
You're even prettier
than any of the girlfriends I've had.
Hey!
That hurt!
What's your lipstick color?
I'm into it.
I have it in my bag.
- Would you like to try?
- Hold on, sweetie.
Let's now enjoy our meal
- before we talk.
- Come on.
- Please dig in.
- Sure.
- Let me have some.
- Would you like some omelet?
Hm...
Honey.
Eat your food!
Go on now!
Mm...
Here.
Dai,
please take care of Jane for me.
I have no idea whether
she's causing trouble at school.
Keep her in her place, would you?
Leave it to me, Mom.
I'll make sure she stays in line.
Dai!
- Dad.
- Huh?
- Eat.
- Mm-hm.
Here you go.
Eat up, honey.
- Here you go, son.
- Alright, Mom.
I'll take care of the dishes.
That can't be. Go wait outside.
I got it.
Dai, go talk to Juss.
I'll take care of it.
I'm the best at dishwashing.
Sweetie, don't!
You broke so many dishes last time.
Just come out here, you.
- Mom!
- Go, and don't bother them.
Come on, let me handle it.
If you insist.
Jane isn't good at chores.
Why are you out here, Dad?
I'm waiting to have a word with you.
You're making quite a serious face.
Jane,
when you told me you were a lesbian,
did you consider
who would take care of you
when you get older
and don't have children?
Well...
Dai and I can take care of each other.
And what if you break up before that?
I don't think this kind of love
will last long.
Then I'll keep it in the fridge.
Now's not the time for jokes.
I'm being serious, sweetie.
Then why do you think a relationship
between women wouldn't last?
I don't think it's relevant.
Even one between a man
and a woman can end.
Look at the auntie next door.
She's divorced.
With Juss,
it took me a long time
to come to terms with it.
Now, it's you.
I don't know where I'd put myself
or even how I could come to accept it.
I believe that if you love me,
my sexual orientation
is not going to be a problem
in our family.
What are you thinking, Dai?
I'm sorry.
For what?
Well...
Besides Ging,
I'm not close to anyone in my family.
When problems come up,
the only thing I do is text my parents.
We never sit down face-to-face
or have a family meal together.
After what I saw today,
I feel even worse.
Your family gave me the warmest welcome,
but...
I can't even take you
to meet my parents.
It's all good.
It's not a problem for me at all.
So don't stress out, okay?
But...
Are you sure you're okay with things
the way they are?
Mm.
I guess I am.
I got used to being independent
because I've been living on my own
since high school.
I don't feel like I'm missing anything,
though I do get lonely sometimes.
I guess you don't get lonely anymore.
'Cause I'll keep you busy.
Thank you, beautiful.
Are you tired today?
Not at all.
It's been so much fun.
What about you?
What do you think about my family?
They're adorable.
I absolutely love them.
Dai?
Yes?
I think...
I have a feeling
that I want to open the door.
Where's your key? Unlock it.
I'll help you find it.
Hey, Dai!
Just kidding.
Jane?
Yes?
Do you know that being together
isn't the end of our journey,
but just the beginning?
Yes.
Once we make it official,
our relationship will be clearer,
and we'll gradually learn
each other's strengths and weaknesses.
There will probably be days
when we fight or disagree,
but we'll get through them together.
Understood?
I do now.
I'll do my absolute best.
I will, too.
I will go all in.
So...
Will you be my girlfriend, Jane?
♫Every time you are near,
I feel at ease♫
♫You're too cute,
no way I can deny that♫
♫You're my comfort zone,
don't let go of me♫
Thank you.
One blended banana milk, please.
Congratulations,
you're the 99th customer of the day.
There's a buy 1 get 1 free deal for you.
Here you go.
Thank you!
Thank you, too.
After the day I said yes
to being Dai's girlfriend,
my life has been graced
with many good things!
Out of the blue, I got
a buy 1 get 1 free deal
for being the 99th customer of the day!
Plus, I'm also lucky in love.
Morning, I miss you.
Morning, miss you, too, Dai.
But the most surprising thing of all
is a message from Dad.
Jane,
bring that senior home
for a meal again sometime.
Sure thing.
But she's not just a senior now.
My life is at the happiest place!
Hello?
Hello, Jane,
my absolutely bombshell and cutie pie!
Right...
I have great news for you.
What is it about?
Our staff has been missing you
so, so much!
So we had a meeting and decided
we want you back on our team!
Right, but...
I don't think I'll have time
to create another comic for you.
I'm having fun writing the GL's one.
Ooh! Ooh!
That's exactly
what I wanted to talk about!
Right now, the website's wanting
to try its hand in that market.
You can go ahead
and publish that comic here.
Hard pass.
When I pitched the idea,
none of you cared to accept it.
All of a sudden,
you want to explore the market?
Isn't that kinda sus?
I think I'll stick to doing it myself.
And please don't contact me
any further.
Goodbye.
Ugh...Jane...
One orange cake, please.
Of course.
Who's with you today?
Oh, it's just me,
but I got really lucky today
with this buy 1 get 1 free deal!
You did?
Yes!
And how did you know I was here?
Is this a coincidence?
Love is never a coincidence.
If I want to see you,
I'll search high and low for you.
Dai, you silly...
Are you blushing, Jane?
I'm not.
Jane?
Yes?
From 1 to 100,
how much would you say you like me?
Hm...
I'd say 200!
Really?
Then, if it gets to 300,
should we talk about
moving in together?
That way, we can do more
than what we used to.
You haven't ordered any drinks.
Here it is.
You already have one for me.
That's right...
Getting red?
Dai!
That's the former Queen of Architecture
who's on the page's news.
Who is she with?
Do you know how sharp your eyes were
looking at me back then?
Like that.
Dai!
Hm?
I have a confession to make.
Actually,
I also looked back at you every time.
I still didn't know how I felt,
but I did know
that I was so weirdly attracted,
that I couldn't help but look.
But, at that time,
you also stared at me,
sometimes
with your arms crossed, too.
That was why I thought
you didn't like me.
That wasn't what happened at all.
Here.
Is it good?
Oh, yeah.
Now, a university fan page
has posted about my dating news.
Let me see.
[There are tons of Janes
on campus, so could you be specific?]
[That can't be; it'd be such a waste
if someone as pretty as Dai likes girls,
and anyone can ride on her pillion, no?
Stop making things up. Not into it]
[Hey, the photo is blurry,
so can I get more info?
Which Jane is that supposed to be?]
[Ooh, Dai being a lesbian got my heart
shaken, but which Jane, though?]
[Anyone have this Jane's social media?
Wanna give her a follow]
This photo...
is gonna get mad views!
What? Champ, where are you going?
You're quite something.
Don't you love me anyway?
Of course.
Silly you.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming, Dad?
Or are you here to spy on me?
No, sweetie.
The reason I'm here
is to apologize to you
about what happened that day.
I just thought you were too young
for this kind of stuff.
But I'm almost 19 now.
In my eyes,
you're still a child no matter what.
It's just that...Dai and I got together
to gradually learn about each other.
We're not talking
about marriage or anything that far.
I know how much you love
and care for me,
but...
isn't it my choice to choose
who I want to spend my life with?
You can't stop me, either,
because...
I'll get mad at you,
and you will miss out on the chance
to have somtam with me all year.
And without me,
there will be lots of leftovers at home
since I have the biggest appetite
out of everyone.
But...
Alright, okay.
But you gotta remember
that I have the right
to keep my eye on you.
I don't want my little girl
to cry her eyes out in the end.
Well, if I ever got hurt,
will you hug me and comfort me, Dad?
I'll be here anytime
and anywhere you want.
Thank you, Dad.
Right, Dad?
Hm?
I have one question
that's always been on my mind.
What is it, sweetie?
Why do all my older siblings
have two-syllable names
but I only have one?
Oh!
This, huh?
Here's the story.
I was actually the one who named you
because your mom's name idea
was tricky to pronounce.
What was it?
Your name actually had three Js.
J-A-J-O-J,
pronounced, 'Ja-joj.'
I think I prefer
the name you gave me.
It's one syllable, but...
I like it!
Right? Good for you.
Otherwise, you would've grown up
being called,
"Ja-joj! Ja-joj!"
Could you imagine
how embarrassing you'd feel?
[Directed by SUEASIAM STUDIO]
You're totally out of the loop.
Jane and Dai
have already moved in together!
Thanks again, JaneWill!
Where did you guys go?
How many people were there?
Just the two of you?
I went there with Kim.
There were two of us.
Wouldn't Dai be mad at me
if she found out?
Have you ever even cared about me?
- I...
- Go on.
I'm waiting for your explanation.